# MARK **NGUYEN**

10501 Petaloma Dr. Orlando FL 32817 · (727) 470 8791 markngn@live.com – marknguyen.live

I graduated with a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering and a Minor Degree in Mathematics at University of Central Florida. I always seek for opportunities to learn more; not only from my field of study but also from any field that relates to computer technology. During my time in school, I interested more in software development, and I have done a few projects that required researching and learning new technologies that were not taught in school. These experience taught me that computer technology is always evolving, so I must continue learning in order to keep updating my knowledge.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2006 – 2010
PAINTER, C&N YATCH REFINISHING

2010 – PRESENT FISHERMAN (SEASONAL), FAMILY FISHING BUSINES

2016 – 2020 E.M.R. (PART TIME), ROBERT K. LAW DOCTORS OFFICE

#### **EDUCATION**

**B.S. COMPUTER ENGINEERING + MATH MINOR**, UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA (UCF)
3.4 GPA

## **SKILLS**

- Proficiency in Java, C, C++, JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, and SQL.
- I am a fast learner, and I am also confident with my interpersonal skill.
- I respond well with stressful situations.

# **ACTIVITIES**

I have worked in 2 group projects that developed 2 webapps. Both of them include developing a front page UI and a background server. The first webapp utilizes a local server that was running in my personal computer. The second webapp uses a cloud based server that was bundled with a registered domain. I also worked in 2 other Android projects. The first project was building a task manager app that manage users' data through a cloud based server. The second project was a graphical application that utilizes any Android device as a display for an EKG machine that my team designed for our senior project before graduation.